dezide.com 2018-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Dezide

Last Updated: May 18, 2018

* * *

Thank you for using the Site and/or Services of Dezide ApS (“Dezide”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). We take your privacy very seriously, and this Privacy Policy explains the ways in which we collect, use, disclose, and protect information relating to our Site and Services.

This Privacy Policy may be amended at any time, with or without notice or notification, so we recommend periodically reviewing it. Continued use of the Site or Services following the posting of any change to this Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of all changes. We suggest printing or saving a local copy of this Privacy Policy for your records.

**Table of Contents**

What Information we collect about you

Automatically collected Information

How we use your information

How we use user content 

The legal basis for collecting the personal data

Data controller and data processors

How we store your Information

How we secure your information

How long we keep your information

How to access and control your information

Changes to the privacy policy

Other important privacy information

Notice to end users

Contact us

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is incorporated into Dezides Terms of Service and License Agreement located at <http://www.dezide.com/terms-of-service> (the “Terms of Service”) and applies to the information obtained by us through your use of Dezides Site, Software, and Services (“Information”) as described in this Policy. ** **

## What Information we collect about you

When you interact with our Site, Software, and/or Services, we collect Information that, alone or in combination with other data, could be used to identify you (“Personal Data”). Some of the Information we collect is stored in a manner that cannot be linked back to you (“Non-Personal Data”).

When you are using the Site, Software, and/or Service, Dezide may collect personal data about you such as your name, company, e-mail address, phone number, address and IP address as well as logging the chat session between you and the Dezide support agent when you submit support tickets (“Personal Data”).

Dezide registers and processes Personal Data to deliver the requested services when you:

  * Are using certain self-services and contact forms,
  * Send us an inquiry or give us feedback,
  * Submit support tickets to our support desk
  * Give any kind of Personal Data to us via our website or applications.

We collect information about you when you input it into the Services or otherwise provide it directly to us, including:

  * **_Account and Profile Information:_** Your username, email address, and contact and language preferences _._  If you log into Dezide with a social networking credential, such as with your Google+ account, we will ask permission to access basic information from that account, such as your name and email address. You can stop sharing that information with us at any time by removing Dezides access to that account. We also store your company’s mailing address in our CRM system if you are the contract responsible for the Service.

  * **_Content you provide through our products_** : User Content. This content includes any information about you that you may choose to include. Examples of content we collect and store include: Names/Titles, Probabilities, Cost, Descriptive Explanations added to Causes, Actions, Questions in Static Guides, Dynamic Guides, and FAQ Articles, comments you enter when committing changes, and any feedback you provide to us. Content also includes the files and links you upload to the Services. If you use an on-premise server or data center version of the Services, we do not host, store, transmit, receive or collect information about you (including your content), except in limited cases, where permitted by your administrator: we collect feedback you provide directly to us through the product and; we collect content using analytics techniques that hash, filter or otherwise scrub the information to exclude information that might identify you or your organization, and we collect clickstream data about how you interact with and use features in the Services. On-premise and data center administrators can disable our collection of this information and prevent this information from being shared with us by blocking transmission at the local network level.

  * **_Information you provide through our support channels:  _**The Services also include our customer support, where you may choose to submit information regarding a problem you are experiencing with a Service. Whether you open a support ticket, speak to one of our representatives directly or otherwise engage with our support team, you will be asked to provide contact information, a summary of the problem you are experiencing, and any other documentation, screenshots or information that would be helpful in resolving the issue.

### Automatically collected Information

Certain data about the devices you use to connect with Dezide and your use of the Site, Software, and/or Services are automatically logged in our systems, including:

  * **_Location information_** _:_  This is the geographic area where you use your computer and mobile devices (as indicated by an Internet Protocol [IP] address or similar identifier) when interacting with our Site, Software, and/or Services. Location information is also used for determining when and where to perform a data synchronization between desktop applications and our servers.

  * **_Log data_** _:_  As with most websites and technology services delivered over the internet, our servers automatically collect data when you access or use our Site, Software, and/or Services and record it in log files or databases. This log data may include the IP address, browser type, and settings, the date and time of use, information about browser configuration, language preferences, and cookie data.

  * **_Usage information_** _:_  This is information about the Dezide Site, Software, and/or Services you use and how you use them. We may also obtain data from our third-party partners and service providers to analyze how users use our Site, Software, and/or Services. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page on the Site and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to better understand and optimize the Site.

  * **_Device information_** _:_  These are data from your computer or mobile device, such as the type of hardware and software you are using (for example, your operating system and browser type), as well as unique device identifiers for devices that are using Dezide Software.

## How we use your information

We use, process, and store your Information as necessary to perform our contract with you and for our legitimate business interests, including:

  * **_To provide the Services and personalize your experience_** : To help us administer our Site, Software, and/or Services, authenticate users for security purposes, provide personalized user features and access, process transactions, conduct research, develop new features, and improve the features, algorithms, and usability of our Site, Software, and/or Services.

  * **_To communicate with you about your use of  our services:_** We will communicate Site, Software, and/or Services, product announcements, and software updates, as well as respond to your requests for assistance, including providing account verification support if you’re having difficulty accessing your account.

  * **_To market, promote and drive engagement with the Services_** : We use your contact information to send you promotional communications that may be of specific interest to you, including by direct marketing emails and special offers about Dezide, from which you can unsubscribe at any time. We will only send you marketing information if you consent to us doing so.

  * **_To provide human User Content review services:_** For users who add content through our products, we may review the content on your request.

  * **_For safety and security:_** We calculate aggregate statistics on the number of unique devices using our Site, Software, and/or Services, and to detect and prevent fraud and misuse of those.

  * **_Customer support_** : We use your information to resolve technical issues you encounter, to respond to your requests for assistance, to analyze crash information, and to repair and improve our products.

Further, Dezide is using the Personal Data and your use of Dezide to give you the best possible advice, for knowledge capturing and analysis purposes, in order to create a complete customer picture and get a bigger understanding on the demands and behaviors of our customers. We utilize this knowledge to create more customized user experiences.

## How we use user content

As a rule, Dezide employees do not monitor or view your User Content stored in or transferred through our Site, Software, and/or Services, but it may be viewed if we believe the Terms of Service have been violated and confirmation is required, if we need to do so to respond to your requests for user support, if we otherwise determine that we have an obligation to review it as described in the Terms of Service. In addition, if you request our human User Content review services, our reviewers may also read the User Content you submit, as necessary to perform our contract with you.

## The legal basis for collecting the personal data

The processing of your Personal Data is based on the understanding between you and Dezide that you will use one or more of our products, and that the processing of your Personal Data is necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes mentioned above. The processing of your Personal Data is thereby considered necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or in order to take steps at the request of you prior to entering into a contract, which is Dezides legal basis for processing your Personal Data (Article 6, para. 1, lit. b of the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679)).

Your Personal Data may only be processed for different purposes if this is necessary in order to comply with legal or regulatory obligations (e.g. transfer to courts or criminal prosecution authorities), if you have consented to the respective processing, or if the processing is otherwise lawful under applicable law. If processing for a different purpose takes place we may provide you with additional information.

## Data controller and data processors

Dezide ApS, Gasværksvej 5, DK-9000 Aalborg, Denmark, telephone +45 96 55 73 70, is responsible for data security and the processing of your Personal Data according to the specific purposes mentioned above.

Dezide can share your Personal Data with third parties acting as Dezides data processors for processing your Personal Data according to the purposes mentioned above.

We only disclose Personal Data to third parties when:

  * We use service providers who assist us in meeting business operations needs, including hosting, delivering, and improving our Services. We also use service providers for specific services and functions, including email communication and analytics. These service providers may only access, process, or store Personal Data pursuant to our instructions and to perform their duties to us.

  * We have your explicit consent to share your Personal Data.

  * We believe it is necessary to investigate potential violations of the Terms of Service, to enforce those Terms of Service, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or potential threats against persons, property, or the systems on which we operate our Site, Software, and/or Services.

  * We determine that the access, preservation, or disclosure of your Personal Data is required by law to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Dezide and users of our Site, Software, and/or Services, or to respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including national security or law enforcement requests.

  * We need to do so in connection with a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, reorganization, the sale of some or all of our assets or stock, a public offering of securities, or steps in consideration of such activities (e.g., due diligence). In these cases, some or all of your Personal Data may be shared with or transferred to another entity, subject to this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose Non-Personal Data publicly and to third parties – for example, in public reports about general Dezide usage, to partners under an agreement with us, or as part of progress reports, we may provide to users.

Dezide does not share your Personal Data with third parties for the purpose of enabling them to deliver their advertisements to you.

## How we store your Information

Information submitted to Dezide through our cloud-based Services will be transferred to, processed, and stored in Data Centers relative to your location. This means, that if your company is located in Europe, we will use European data centers and if your company is located in the United States, we will use a data center in the United States accordingly. This is done to ensure proper performance of the Services.

For customers using our on-premise or data center options, data is stored as local IT sees fit. This is outside of Dezides responsibility.

When you use the Software on your computing device, User Content you save will be stored locally on that device and synced with our servers. If you post or transfer any Information to or through our Site, Software, and/or Services, you are agreeing to such Information, including Personal Data and User Content, being hosted and accessed in that location.

### How we secure your information

Dezide is committed to protecting the security of your Information and takes reasonable precautions to protect it. However, Internet data transmissions, whether wired or wireless, cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and as a result, we cannot ensure the security of Information you transmit to us, including Personal Data and User Content; accordingly, you acknowledge that you do so at your own risk.

We use industry-standard encryption to protect your data in transit. This is commonly referred to as transport layer security (“TLS”) or secure socket layer (“SSL”) technology.

Once we receive your data, we protect it on our servers using a combination of technical, physical, and logical security safeguards. The security of the data stored locally in any of our Software installed on your computing device requires that you make use of the security features of your device. We recommend that you take the appropriate steps to secure all computing devices that you use in connection with our Site, Software, and Services.

If Dezide learns of a security system breach, we may attempt to notify you and provide information on protective steps, if available, through the email address that you have provided to us or by posting a notice on the Site. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive such notices in writing.

If you use on-premise or data center Services, responsibility for securing storage and access to the information you put into the Services rests with you and not Dezide. We strongly recommend that on-premise or data center users configure SSL to prevent interception of data transmitted over networks and to restrict access to the databases and other storage points used.

## How long we keep your information

We store your Personal Data only for as long as this is necessary for the above-mentioned purposes, namely to deliver the requested services to you, to communicate with you, to allow the Dezide support team to search for previous incident reports involving you and as long as necessary to create more customized user experiences for you.

Some of your Personal Data may, however, be stored for accounting purposes or for defense of legal claims. This Personal Data will be stored until the expiration of the statutory limitation period. Moreover, some of your Personal Data may be stored in an anonymized form that does not allow you to be identified.

## How to access and control your information

You have the right to request a copy of your information, to object to our use of your information (including for marketing purposes), to request the deletion or restriction of your information, or to request your information in a structured, electronic format. Below, we describe the tools and processes for making these requests.

Where the Services are administered for you by an administrator (see “Notice to End Users” below), you may need to contact your administrator to assist with your requests first. For all other requests, you may contact us as provided in the Contact Us section below to request assistance.

Your request and choices may be limited in certain cases: for example, if fulfilling your request would reveal information about another person, or if you ask to delete information which we or your administrator are permitted by law or have compelling legitimate interests to keep.

  * **_Access and update your information_** : You cannot update your profile information within our products. This is managed by an Administrator and hence, you need to contact an Administrator for making changes to your profile (see “Notice to End Users” below). You can modify content that contains information about you using the editing tools associated with that content adhering to your permissions in the product.

  * **_Deactivate your account_** : If you no longer wish to use our services, your administrator needs to delete your account as this is not possible by End Users in the product. If you are an administrator an wish to cancel your contract with Dezide, you must contact us as provided in the Contact Us section below to request assistance.

  * **_Delete your information/right to be forgotten:_** Our Services give you the ability to delete certain information about you from within the Service. For example, you can remove content that contains information about you using editing tools associated with that content. However, please note that we may need to retain certain information about you for record keeping purposes. For Example: the version control system keeps an audit log of all modifications performed in the Dezide Administration to enable tracking of all changes. Likewise, we will retain usage information adhering to your use of the service for aggregated telemetry purposes. Should you wish us to delete the Personal Information that we have on file for you, you can request deletion by contacting us as provided in the Contact Us section below. Such requests will normally result in deletion of your contact record in the CRM system, and you will also be unsubscribed from any subsequent marketing Emails. Such requests will be processed normally within two weeks.

  * **_Opt out of  communications_** ** _:  _**You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by using the unsubscribe link within each email, or by contacting us as provided below to have your contact information removed from our promotional email list or registration database. Even after you opt out from receiving promotional messages from us, you will continue to receive transactional messages from us regarding our Services.

  * **_Request that we stop using your information_** :  In some cases, you may ask us to stop accessing, storing, using and otherwise processing your information where you believe we don’t have the appropriate rights to do so.  For example, if you are no longer an active user, you can request that we delete your account as provided in this policy. Where you gave us consent to use your information for a limited purpose, you can contact us to withdraw that consent, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place at the time. When you make such requests, we may need time to investigate and facilitate your request.

## Changes to the privacy policy

We reserve the right to change or supplement this Privacy Notice at any time. The current Privacy Notice will always be available on Grundfos’ company website.

## Other important privacy information

### Notice to end users

Our products are intended for use by organizations. Where the Services are made available to you through an organization (e.g. your employer), that organization is the administrator of the Services and is responsible for the accounts and/or Service sites over which it has control. If this is the case, please direct your data privacy questions to your administrator, as your use of the Services is subject to that organization’s policies. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of an administrator’s organization, which may be different than this policy.

Administrators are able to:

  * restrict, suspend or terminate your access to the Services;
  * access information in and about your account;
  * access or retain information stored as part of your account;
  * change the email address associated with your account;
  * change your information, including profile information;
  * restrict your ability to edit, restrict, modify or delete information

Even if the Services are not currently administered to you by an organization, if you use an email address provided by an organization (such as your work email address) to access the Services, then the owner of the domain associated with your email address (e.g. your employer) may assert administrative control over your account and use of the Services at a later date.

## Contact us

Dezide ApS  
Gasværksvej 5  
9000 Aalborg Denmark  
(+45) 9655 7370  
info@dezide.com
